 Hi! I’m Arya Burke, and this is the readme for my conference project for Mike Siff’s Spring 2019 Databases course. In this conference project I analyzed a database of deleted Russian propaganda tweets, accounts used primarily to influence the 2016 election. I had a lot of fun and a lot of challenges doing this project. One of the most challenging things was the data. Because the data is static and not connected to the Twitter API, a lot of the pathways for analysis I wanted to follow were impossible without connecting to an active Twitter server. For instance, it turned out that most retweets were not of other bot accounts but of other Twitter accounts, and so I could not access the statistics for favorites and retweets of tweets that weren’t stored in the database. This made doing any sort of tweet chain analysis really challenging. Hopefully the menu will explain itself! Another fascinating thing I discovered near the end is that bots do not engage with each other’s retweets *at all.* You can favorite and retweet a retweet, but every single retweet by a bot has 0 of both. It makes sense to me, as it reveals the lack of necessity of active retweets to contribute to supporting a popular account. It also shows that popular bots never retweet other bots, as human accounts might like their retweets. Hopefully you are as interested as I have been in imagining the structure and strategy of a massive-scale mobilization of social media to influence elections!